netgame.com 2006-12-09

# ::: Welcome to Netgame :::

|  |   
---  
| 

| Modified - July. 2006

The Company (Mgame USA Inc.) highly respects the privacy of its online users and recognizes the importance of providing a secure environment. Therefore, the Company has established this Privacy Policy, which outlines 1) the necessary information to be collected, 2) the body of the information collection, 3) the usage of the collected information, 4) how the Company treats the privacy protection for children.

You will open an account with the Company by registering. Though the Company may share your data with the Company affiliates with varying personal data protection laws, your data is always protected by our Privacy Policy.

This privacy policy applies to the following web sites (the "Websites) operated by Mgame USA Inc.:  
netgame.com, legendofares.com

In addition, the Company owns several other domain names that point to the Web Sites listed above, and we will from time to time add new sites that may or may not be listed above. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to sites maintained by the Company (Mgame USA Inc.) and not to web sites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link.

The Company does not guarantee the security of any of users' private transmissions against any unauthorized or unlawful interception or access by disapproved third parties.  
  
---  
**1)** | **The Necessary Information to be Collected.**  
| The Company may collect certain Personal Information on the voluntary basis when Members register to use our websites and games. Collected personal information may include Members' names, e-mail addresses, home addresses, phone numbers, birth-dates. Members will also be asked to submit other Personal Information depending on their selected methods of the payment and billing.  
The Company may use Cookies on its websites. "Cookies" are small bit of record-keeping information stored on users computers. After a set-ups of cookies on websites, users would not have to re-type their passwords more than once, thereby they will be able to save some time when they are using our websites. If users reject cookies, they may still use websites, however their access will be limited in some areas or may have to enter passwords or identifying information more than once.  
The Company also collects other information of a non-personal nature, such as IP addresses, browser types, domain names, software versions, and access times for its internal purposes.  
The Company may also collect Personal Information from at other points on its websites which require user input.  
**2)** | **The Body of the Information Collection**  
| The provided information will be collected by the Company only.   
Location of the Company: Irvine, CA  
**3)** | **The Usage of the Collected Information**  
| The Company uses collected Personal Information to provide users with its products (such as "The Legend of Ares", "Hero Online" or other games) and services that are tailored specifically to the provided profiles. In connection with the delivery of its services, the Company may share the personal information with third-party partners or vendors that assist the Company for the delivery or administration of the services, however they will be strictly permitted only to use the information in connection with the delivery or administration of our services. The Company uses user's information on an aggregated basis (not personally identifiable) to do such things as operating/enhancing its websites and sending and delivering messages. The Company may disclose aggregated information only, and this information will not contain any Personal Information.  
Due to legal rules beyond its control, the Company can (and users authorize it to) disclose any information about users to private entities (i.e. credit bureaus and other entities/organizations legally entitled to this information), law enforcement agencies or government officials, as it, in our sole discretion, believes that it is necessary or appropriate to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, the Company may share Personal Information with its contractors on a need-to-know basis in order to maintain our provided services, and such contractors will guarantee of the non-disclosure and confidentiality of Personal Information.  
**4)** | **How the Company Treats the Privacy Protection for Children**  
| The Company does not collect or store any Personal Information of children. The definition of "children" is those who are under the minimum age-limit specified in the eligibility of the game." In order for children to use the Service, their parent(s) or guardian(s) must complete the registration process, open an Account under their name(s) and accept full responsibility for all obligations on "The User Agreement." The Company urges parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, address, or phone numbers, without permission. 

By using websites, Members agree with this Privacy Policy, however it is subject to change at any time upon the necessity. The Company encourages Members to review this document regularly. 

Should you have any question, please feel free to send your inquiry to   
[privacy@mgameusa.com](mailto:privacy@mgameusa.com).
